Arrington Dixon
DC Public Library Special Collections
Arrington Dixon Papers
1964-2008
DC Public Library, Special Collections
14 cubic feet; 14 boxes
132
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series 1
  - Contribution/Fundraising/Voter Outreach Materials/Event Invitations, 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Speeches/Talking Point Outlines/Campaign Planning Notes, 1976-1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - DC Voters Surveys and Questionnaires, 1978-1892 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Campaign Advertisement, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Notes and Agenda Minutes, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Voting Education Pamphlets and Handouts, 1976-1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Receipts/Budget Outlines/Expenditure Reports/Quotes/Estimates, 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "The Get Out The Vote Master Action Plan", 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases/Articles/Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Evelyn F. Murphy Campaign Advance Manual, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Campaign Memorabilia, 1976-1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Guest Books, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Contribution Forms, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Budgets and Expenses, 1978-1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Procedure Outlines and Strategy Plan Documents, 1976-1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Position Papers, 1974-1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Arrington Dixon Campaign Committee, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - James W. Dixon (1 of 2), 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - James W. Dixon (2 of 2), 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Schedules (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Schedules (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Schedules and Events, 1976-1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - James Dixon Awards and Workbooks, 1953-1961 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - James Dixon Personal Inventory/Letters/Programs, 1964-1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Pamphlets and Programs, 1954-1964 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Address Book, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Photographs and Negatives, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Flyers/Invitations/Programs/Journals/Agendas, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - The Budget of the District of Columbia FY 77, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - The Budget of the District of Columbia FY 78, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The Budget of the District of Columbia FY 79, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - The Budget of the District of Columbia FY 80, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - The District of Columbia Capital Project Financing, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Answers to Questions, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Questionnaire, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Statements and Press Releases, 1978-1982 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - AD Speeches, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Campaign Literature and Position Papers (1 of 3), 1978-1982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Literature and Position Papers (2 of 3), 1978-1982 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Campaign Literature and Position Papers (3 of 3), 1978-1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Ads/Prospectus/Contacts, 1974-1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Ads/Pictures/Negatives, Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Legislation Introduced by Council Members Arrington Dixon (1 of 3), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Legislation Introduced by Council Members Arrington Dixon (2 of 3), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Legislation Introduced by Council Members Arrington Dixon (3 of 3), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - June Correspondence, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - July Correspondence, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - August Correspondence, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - September Correspondence, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - October Correspondence, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - November Correspondence, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Calendar of Events, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Calendar of Events, 1975-04 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Calendar of Events, 1975-03 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - August Correspondence, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - August Calendar, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - September Calendar, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence File, 1975-09 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence File, 1975-10 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Calendar, 1975-10 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Calendar, 1975-11 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Calendar, 1975-12 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Calendar (Old Events), 1975-02 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - April Correspondence, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence File, 1975-03 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Note from the Desk of Ruth McClain, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Contact Information for Julius Washington and Brad Gillian, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence File, 1975-01 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence File, 1975-02 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence File, 1975-05 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Calendar, 1975-06 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1975-06 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1975-07 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Calendar, 1975-07 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - News Releases (1 of 2), 1981-01 - 1981-06 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - News Releases (2 of 2), 1981-01 - 1981-06 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Photographs/Newsletters/Certificate, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Arrington Dixon Clippings, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Arrington Dixon Resume, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Speeches, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - News Releases, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Inaugural Activites, 1975-1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Congressional Record, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - The District of Columbia Taxicab Columbia Taxicab Commision News Clippings, Undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - News Releases, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Inaugural Activites, 1975-1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Congressional Record, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - The District of Columbia Taxicab Columbia Taxicab Commision News Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Comprehensive Planning Document: Arrington Dixon/Chariman/D.C. City Council, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - A Survey of Voter Attitudes and Opinions, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Appendix C: Tabulations - Volume I, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - A Visit Through Our History: Historical DC Council Photos, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - May Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - April Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Calendar, 1976-03 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - April Calendar, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Calendar, 1976-01 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - December Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - June Correspondence, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - July Correspondence, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - August Correspondence, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - September Correspondence, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - October Correspondence, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - November Correspondence, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Copywrites, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence/Letters/Programs, 1959-1968 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - High School Leadership Materials/Military Photographs, 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Corespondence/Notes/Student ID/Drawings, 1961-1964 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - District of Columbia Taxicab Commission, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Certificates/Programs/Manuals/Invitations/McKinley Campaign Speech, 1953-1987 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Certificates, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Newsletters, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Update and Inquiry Procedures for the Dixon Constituency File, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings (1 of 6), 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings (2 of 6), 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings (3 of 6), 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings (4 of 6), 1978-1980 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings (5 of 6), 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings (6 of 6), 1987 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - James Dixon Newspaper Clippings/Pamphlets/Letters, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Greeting Cards, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Negatives, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Democratic National Convention Delegate Passes, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Young Adults for Arrington Dixon Getaway Brochure, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Personal and Family Pictures, Undated (Box 14, Folder 11)